styledecordeals.com 2017-02-04

# Style, Decor & More: PRIVACY POLICY

Privacy Policy for Style, Decor & More. If you do not find the information you are looking for below or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact me by email at styledecor1@gmail.com.

At www.styledecordeals.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.stylendecordeals.com/and how it is used.

**Privacy Statement**

If and to the extent that you submit any personal data (such as your name and email address) to Style, Décor & More through this Blog, Style, Décor & More confirms that it will only use any such personal data for the purposes for which you have provided such data. No private information will be given or sold to anyone, including sponsored events such as giveaways, etc. However, if you submit personal data to any sellers or resellers with which you discovered on the Blog, I disclaim any liability and responsibility with respect to the use and security of information by sellers or resellers.

**Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, www.styledecordeals.com/ makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

www.stylendecordeals.com/ does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.stylendecordeals.blogspot.com/.

.:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to www.styledecordeals.com/ and other sites on the Internet.

.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include:  

Google Adsense

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.styledecordeals.com/ send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.  

www.styledecordeals.com/ has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.styledecordeals.com/'s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.  
  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see:[http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)
